# Marisa Vukas

As a Full-Stack Software Engineer with a passion for music production and playing the violin for over a decade, I bring a unique perspective to my work. Skilled in C#, JavaScript, Angular, React, Node, numerous SQL databases, and Music Technology. Highly driven, self-motivated, and enjoys working in a team environment.

# **EXPERIENCE**

Baker Hill, Carmel, IN — Associate Software Developer

JANUARY 2024 - DECEMBER 2024

- Worked on a multi-tenant SAAS loan origination software platform hosted in Microsoft Azure datacenters in the Fintech industry.
- Collaborated with other developers, testers, business analysts and stakeholders to deliver high-quality software solutions at speed.
- Translated business needs to Azure DevOps Features, User Stories, Tasks with estimates, as part of an Agile SDLC.
- Designed and delivered Angular components for user data entry.
- Designed and delivered WebAPI endpoints as solutions for business requirements in a C#, n-tier architecture.
- · Leveraged Azure cloud-native technology (Azure Tables, Blobs, Functions, etc.) for third-party API integrations.
- Conducted unit testing and debugging to ensure the stability and reliability of software applications.

# Winthrop Capital Management, Carmel, IN — Software Engineer

SEPTEMBER 2023 - DECEMBER 2023

- Proficient in C# and .NET framework, with experience in Entity Framework for database interaction.
- Completed code refactoring tasks in an Agile software development environment.

Edify Labs, Fishers, IN — Workflow Developer

NOVEMBER 2022 - APRIL 2023

- Created configurations for companies in our sales pipeline.
- Acted as a technical resource within the team, providing support in resolving workflow-related challenges, including those involving APIs and databases.
- Utilized ongoing creative and innovative ideas to leverage the Edify API, with the goal of continuously enhancing and streamlining customer service efficiency.

d2index, Westminster, CO - Software Engineer Intern

2022 - 2023

# https://d2index.com/

- My duties included designing and implementing UIs in React.js, resolving bugs, and participating in a product-driven agile process.
- Built reusable UI components using styled-components to increase scalability and reusability.
- Built RESTful APIs that served data to the React front-end.
- Designed and implemented UIs in React.js, using a mobile first philosophy.
- Worked on a 3D NFT Gallery Prototype, which allows users to walk through a gallery of purchased NFTs with a first-person camera using React Three Fiber.
- Assembled cryptocurrency graphs using Chart.js and REST APIs.

# **PROJECTS**

# Poblano's Grill Web App — https://aithub.com/marisavukas/poblanos

• A fully responsive restaurant app built with React and Node.js

Website Portfolio App — <a href="https://github.com/marisavukas/react-bootstrap-portfolio">https://github.com/marisavukas/react-bootstrap-portfolio</a>

• Responsive single-page app featuring my personal projects and resume built with React, Bootstrap, and Node.js.

Online Metronome App — <a href="https://github.com/marisavukas/metronome">https://github.com/marisavukas/metronome</a>

Responsive app made from scratch using React, Node, js and Tone. js library.

# **EDUCATION**

Purdue University, West Lafayette, IN — Bachelor of Science, Nutrition Science MAY 2020

#### CONTACT

marisavukas@gmail.com

## LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marisa-vukas/

## **Portfolio**

marisavukas.com

## **SKILLS**

## Languages

- · C#
- JavaScript
- HTML
- · CSS
- Flexbox
- Grid
- TypeScript

### Frameworks

- ·.NET
- Cypress
- · React/Redux
- Angular
- BootStrap
- · Node.js
- · Three.js
- · Tone.js
- · Express.js
- · Styled-components

# **TOOLS**

- ·SOL
- · PostgreSQL
- · GitHub
- · Heroku